<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Theses on LOCS</title><link>/theses/</link><description>Recent content in Theses on LOCS</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/theses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Machine Learning approach to detect Malicious Web servers based on Whois and DNS Information</title><link>/theses/ml-approach-malicious-webservers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/ml-approach-malicious-webservers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ADT Dataset Creation</title><link>/theses/adt-dataset-creation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-dataset-creation/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Write code that creates a LOT of ADTs in standardized format (xml/json) from some kind of dataset (example: MITRE). This could be used for general analysis or as training data for some kind of ML project.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ADT Industry Survey</title><link>/theses/adt-is/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-is/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Interview a series of people in industry who work with ADTs to find how they use them, why they use them, how they are perceived (what do they find useful), etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ADT JSON Format</title><link>/theses/adt-json-format/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-json-format/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Describe and define a JSON format for ADTs. Write code that will convert between the defined ADTool XML ADT format to a new defined JSON ADT format.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ADT Kill Chain Mapping</title><link>/theses/adt-kcm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-kcm/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Create a parameter that can map an ADT node to a kill chain step. Provide examples of this mapping in action. Discuss utility of such a mapping&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ADT Online Survey</title><link>/theses/adt-os/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-os/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Create a survey to be given either in-person or via crowdsourcing that seeks to understand the comprehensibility of attack trees to laypeople.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ADT Python Library</title><link>/theses/adt-python-library/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-python-library/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Create a library that allows for the creation of ADTs in Python. This should include some kind of visualization, the ability to enter whole trees in standard format, and the ability to access/adjust/add onto nodes already within the ADT (needs to ability to traverse and access nodes in the Tree)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ADT Web App Interface</title><link>/theses/adt-web-app-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-web-app-interface/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Develop an interface for a web application to build ADTs&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ADT Web App User Study</title><link>/theses/adt-user-study/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-user-study/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Design and run a user study on the usability of the previously built ADT Web App tool. Find what the strengths and weaknesses of the tool are in a scientific manner.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>An Exploration of C2 Server Fingerprinting Capabilities with Probed HTTP Data</title><link>/theses/c2-detection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/c2-detection/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Analysis of exploit code published on GitHub</title><link>/theses/exploit-code-github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/exploit-code-github/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Automated ADT Format from Image</title><link>/theses/adt-from-image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-from-image/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Write code that can take ADT image and generate a standardized ADT format from it&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Automated ADT Generation</title><link>/theses/automated-adt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/automated-adt/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Write code that can take ADT input in some format: plaintext description, paragraph, structure sentences (BSc), etc, and produce an ADT directly usable format (xml/json)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Automated Dynamic Analysis of Java Exploit Proof-of-Concepts</title><link>/theses/automated-java-pocs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/automated-java-pocs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Automated Dynamic Analysis of Python Exploit Proof-of-Concepts</title><link>/theses/automated-python-pocs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/automated-python-pocs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Establishing a means to collect, store, and query ADT information from a web application</title><link>/theses/adt-webapp-backend-server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/adt-webapp-backend-server/</guid><description/></item><item><title>General Threat Communication Survey</title><link>/theses/gtcs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/gtcs/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Create a survey to be given either in-person or via crowdsourcing to establish what information is received when threats are communicated. How does this information change based on how the threat is communicated?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Measuring non-technical practices during the software development process</title><link>/theses/measure-non-technical-practices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/measure-non-technical-practices/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In spite of all efforts to improve software security, vulnerabilities are still distributed in software. While producing secure software, there are problems with not only purely technical practices but also non-technical practices, such as organizational, behavioral, and governance aspects. People, who make decisions have less understanding of non-technical practices. In this project, you will explore which non-technical practices are involved in the secure software methodologies and the methods used to provide evidence of the effectiveness of these practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Simple Text to ADT</title><link>/theses/text-to-adt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/theses/text-to-adt/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Develop a language with simple grammar that will allow especially non-technically inclined people to write instructions to create an ADT.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>